Hunter Posey

Mountain View, California 94041 | 205-495-7446 | <u>ihunterposey@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Github</u> | <u>Medium</u>

SUMMARY

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript based programming with knowledge of various frameworks within JavaScript, such as React. My Research and studies in Environmental Science and GIS technologies helped me to attain the skills necessary in problem solving, leadership, and teamwork that drive the production of amazing software.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React, HTML/CSS, Git, Linux, Adobe Creative Suite(Photoshop, Illustrator, XD), jQuery, JSON, postGres, WireFraming, arcGIS, ESRI.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Vinylfy - Github | Demo

Vinylfi connects users/sellers to the niche market of buying/selling vinyl records in a fun and easy to use manner.

- Utilized sessions storage to create and persist user data.
- Implemented Auth for all new user information.
- Constructed analytical functions from the backend.

Sopranos Quote-Taker - Github | Demo

A simple and fun app where users can keep track of their favorite Sopranos quotes.

- Full CRUD
- SPA(Single Page Application)

AirDok - Github(Frontend)| Github(Backend) | Demo

A functional app that connects users to private airplane hangar owners to rent/reserve their services.

- Implemented the use of token storage
- Backend Models Authenticated for signup/login
- Used serializers for the backend to allow ease of use for the complex relationships.
- Data is user generated with room for stretch goals to be easily implemented.
- JWT used in the backend

EXPERIENCE

Genesis Capital Ventures

Executive Assistant

Aspen, Colorado 01/2015 - 05/2015

- Created contracts for approximately 30 high-value clients per week.
- Maintained client-relationships through 5-6 phone meetings per week.
- Met with clients face-to-face on a weekly basis.
- Managed all client payments of over \$500,000.00

Mountain High Outfitters

Back-of-house Manager

University of Alabama

Tuscaloosa, Alabama 06/2016 - 02/2019

- Oversaw back-of-house operations(shipments, ordering, moving product, inventory).
- Managed \$25,000.00 worth of inventory.
- Assisted an average of 20 customers per day in regards to their needs.
- Lead opening and closing procedures 4-5 days per week.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School

San Francisco, California 11/2020 - 03/2021

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

Tuscaloosa, Alabama

BA in Environmental Geography/GIS

05/2019